http://www.hohchurch.org/privacy-statement/

Search for:
Privacy Statement
Thank you for visiting hohchurch.org, The House of Hope Presbyterian Church website. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.
THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT
At hohchurch.org, you can subscribe to email lists, request information be sent to you in the mail, among other things. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information and bank account information. We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer, Firefox, etc.), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OS) and the domain name of you Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink, etc.).
HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION
We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our programs, and to respond to your inquires about our offerings.
We will never sell or exchange your information to any third party, without your explicit permission. We may request demographic information that helps us match appropriate information to you. However, the demographic information will only be distributed internally. We will never release your individually identifiable information.
PERSONAL INFORMATION
We will only collect personal identifiable information that you voluntarily provide to us in registering for services. We limit internal access to your information to employees responsible for conducting business with you.
E-MAIL ADDRESSES
We ask subscribers who register for our online services to provide us with their e-mail addresses so we can send them news briefings and account information. We also ask for e-mail addresses from people who want to receive our free e-mail updates. These addresses are used only to send news updates and account information. The House of Hope Presbyterian Church never sells, rents or lends e-mail addresses to anyone.
COOKIES
To enhance your experience with hohchurch.org, some of our web pages use “cookies.” Cookies are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personal identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering for one of our email newsletters. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to data stored in the cookie.
We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on mary.org. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages, to recognize you by name when you return to our site, and to enable you to use a shopping cart on our site.
EXTERNAL LINKS
This site contains links to other sites. The House of Hope Presbyterian Church is not responsible for the privacy practices, or content, of those sites. All external sites will open in a new browser. The House of Hope Presbyterian Church does not endorse external site.
HOW TO CONTACT US
If you have any questions or concerns about this policy or its implementation, you may contact us by calling 651.227.6311, or by using our mailing address, which is The House of Hope Presbyterian Church, 797 Summit Avenue, Saint Paul, MN 55105.
Upcoming Events
Fri
11
Women’s Breakfast Book Group
December 11 @ 7:00 am8:30 am
Fri
11
7@7 – Advent Morning Prayer
(651) 227-6311Follow us on Facebook / Follow us on Instagram
